A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, Annual Reports, Record Group 3, Series 5 FA1745
Rockefeller Archive Center
Social Science Research Council records, Annual Reports, Record Group 3, Series 5
1923-1972, 1977-1978, 1996-1998
Rockefeller Archive Center
Social Science Research Council
FA1745
30 Bound Volumes 30 bound volumes
Arrangement
Chronological
Scope and Contents
Contains Social Science Research Council annual reports 1945-1972, 1977-1978, and 1996-1998.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of the RAC.
Annual reports
- Social Science Research Council Annual Reports, 1923-1972, 1977-1978, 1996-1998; 5; 30 Bound Volumes 30 bound volumes
  Arrangement
  Chronological
  Annual reports
  - SSRC Annual Report 1923-1933 (Item REF 300 SOC 1923-33)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1933-1940 (Item REF 300 SOC 1933-40)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1941-1947 (Item REF 300 SOC 1941-47)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1945-1946 (Item REF 300.9 SOC 1945/46)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1947-1948 (Item REF 300.9 SOC 1947-48)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1949-1950 (Item REF 300.9 SOC 1949-50)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1951-1952 (Item REF 300.9 SOC 1951-52)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1948-1953 (Item REF 300 SOC 1948-53)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1952-1953 (Item REF 300.9 SOC 1952-53)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1953-1954 (Item REF 300.9 SOC 1953/54)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1954-1955 (Item REF 300.9 SO 1954-55)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1955-1956 (Item REF 300.9 SOC 1955-56)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1956-1957 (Item REF 300.9 SOC 1956-57)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1957-1958 (Item REF 300.9 SOC 1957-58)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1958-1959 (Item REF 300.9 SOC 1958-59)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1959-1960 (Item REF 300.9SOC 1959-60)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1960-1961 (Item REF 300.9 SOC 1960-61)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1961-1962 (Item REF 300.9 SOC 1961-62)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1962-1963 (Item REF 300.9 SOC 1962-63)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1963-1964 (Item REF 300.9 SOC 1963-64)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1964-1965 (Item REF 300.9 SOC 1964-65)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1965-1966 (Item REF 300.9 SOC 1965-66)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1966-1967 (Item REF 300.9 SOC 1966-67)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1967-1968 (Item REF 300.9 SOC 1967-68)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1968-1969 (Item REF 300.9 SOC 1968-69)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1969-1970 (Item REF 300.9 SOC 1969-70)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1970-1971 (Item REF 300.9 SOC 1970-71)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1971-1972 (Item REF 300.9 SOC 1971-72)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1977-1978 (Item REF 300.9 SOC 1977-78)
  - SSRC Annual Report 1996-1998 (Item REF 300.9 SOC 1996-98)